so let's go ahead and click on Unity Hub then click on this new project
button it will open up this window right here you can click on this all in
order to see all of the pipelines right so as you can see the below pipelines are
not downloaded the ones which are downloaded is at the top right here a white
so we will be using the 3D build and render pipeline white I'm gonna name this
project as fbs zombie then I'm gonna click on create project so as you can
see right here the project is created we have the scene right here the sample
scene everything else is include view or white scene in a metal game let's
click on scene I will change the mode to share a shared Chrome mode and I'm
gonna turn on the gizmos all right the effects are already drawn on so with the
project created what we're gonna do is in the next video we're gonna add the
environment and then we will start fixing the environment right so catch you
guys in the next one